[theme music playing]
-[gunshot]
-[Ivy] You monster!
You buried my mother alive?!
[Tonio] But if your mother is still alive,
it's possible that the Ardientes have her.
[Diego] Why is she always with Mom?
What does she need from my family?
Why is she in Poblacion Ardiente?
Let's say that she is Lily.
Then why does she need to pretend?
That's what I need to find out.
Everything you've worked
so hard for is crumbling down.
I don't know what to do. I need you.
Maybe this woman triggers
something from her past.
[Raul] Her memories can't return.
It might be better for her
to live as Jasmin
for the rest of her life.
[Diego] Who ordered you to do this?
[man] It's Natalie!
Thank you for coming to save me.
Good news. Your dad is awake.
What?! What will happen
when Papa comes back?
My life's going to be miserable again.
Papa has no reason to return here.
Or he shouldn't return at all.
[Arnaldo] Why didn't you tell me
Grandpa's recovered?
I'll tell Grandpa you were so busy
taking over for him here.
I'm going to bring him home.
-[whimpering] Lily… Lily…
-[Belen] Jasmin?
Who is Lily?
[Ivy] Jepoy, someone took my mom.
They replaced her with
another body to fake her death.
[Jepoy] What's your plan?
[Ivy] I'm going to dig up
all of Emilia's skeletons,
and bring her fears to life.
You had a whole family murdered?
All of them.
Because when I tell my men
to do a good job,
it is indeed a good job.
Why are you so curious
about that family's story?
Why all of a sudden, Ivy?
Very good, Emilia. Very good.
I'm just testing
how you're going to answer
the press during your campaign.
And I think you're more than ready.
-Senator Emilia is ready.
-[chuckles]
So, tell me when you want to start,
so I can send my team here.
Thank you, Ivy.
You know, I really can't wait. Thank you.
You're most welcome.
[chuckles coyly]
Anyway, I have to go.
Okay. Oh, wait.
This weekend is Arnaldo's birthday.
Let's talk some more.
Mm-hm. Sure, Emilia.
Take care.
[tense music playing]
Grandpa, I'm sorry
I couldn't call earlier.
I didn't know you were already
awake. Mom didn't tell me.
[weakly] It's okay, grandson.
We both know how incompetent
your mother is.
All she had to do
was pass down information…
but she couldn't even do it properly.
Well, I think the reason is she
doesn't want you to come back.
She's not happy that I'm getting better?
Well, she's been planning to
replace you in the senate bid.
Se-- [chuckles laboriously]
Senatorial bid.
That woman is delusional.
Well, you know what they say.
"When the cat is away…
the mice will play."
But don't worry, when the cat comes back…
he'll crush all of the mice's ambitions.
That's all they are…
ambitious mice.
[ominous music playing]
[exhales]
[inhales sharply]
[sinister music playing]
[door lock rattling]
[Belen] Raul…
Do we really need to lock Jasmin up?
Can't she just stay here outside?
That's what's best for her.
[bangs on door, sobs]
It'd be better for her
to learn to talk again.
That's not true. I don't believe that.
You saw her, right?
It's just going to hurt her more.
And I don't care what the doctor said.
[sobbing]
[banging on door]
[sobs]
[pensive music playing]
Auntie, trust me, this is
what's best for Jasmin.
But, Raul…
Auntie, please just do as I say.
[sobbing]
[engine stops]
[grunting]
Diego?
[somber music playing]
Ivy Aguas…
are you a mystery to me
because of my feelings for you,
or do I have feelings for you
because you're a mystery?
[Ivy] Emilia won't elaborate on anything.
She's still a tough nut to crack.
But, dear, maybe she really
doesn't know anything.
It's possible.
But it's also possible she does,
and she's just good at hiding.
And Arnaldo?
Arnaldo might be on to this, too.
I'm going to find out
at his birthday party.
How about you? What'd you learn?
Well…
I went to each of these
missing persons' houses…
and I found out one thing.
Most of them were on Emilia's hit list…
-and Tonio was the hit man.
-Oh, god.
That's why we still need Tonio,
because he holds the answer
to my mother's whereabouts.
[tense music playing]
Who are you, Ivy Aguas?
You never told me anything
about your family.
It's like you don't want
anyone entering your world.
Is that why you're avoiding me?
[exhales]
-[door opens]
-[Ivy] Take care.
[tense music playing]
What are you doing here, Madrigal?
Mr. Mayor, you surprised me.
You even brought wine.
Is there something we need to celebrate?
I asked a question, I expect an answer.
What is Madrigal doing here?
Oh, no, Madrigal…
-Should we tell him now?
-What is going on?
[tense music playing]
Mr. Mayor…
[sighs loudly]
I didn't want to tell him, but then…
I guess we don't have a choice, Madrigal.
We have to tell Mr. Mayor everything.
You see, Mr. Mayor…
I called your number one man over…
to ask him what kind of gift
you might like,
because your birthday's coming up soon.
A gift?
Yes, a gift.
But then…
all our efforts have gone
down the drain now, Mr. Mayor,
since you're already here
and found us out.
I just thought that you've given
me so many opportunities
here in Poblacion Ardiente.
So…
I thought of giving you a nice
gift to make it up to you.
But now, the cat's out of the bag.
Miss Aguas is right, Mayor.
She called me over
to ask what your likes are.
So she could prepare her gift for you.
[tense music playing]
[clicks tongue] You really know
how to please, Miss Aguas.
[chuckles]
You didn't have to, but I appreciate it.
Well researched.
Of course.
But then, you already spoiled
our surprise, Mr. Mayor.
I'm sorry.
[clicks tongue]
I just have to wait and see.
Okay.
[chuckles]
[tense music playing]
[somber music playing]
[bangs on door]
[breathing heavily]
[sobbing]
[sobbing continues]
[breathing heavily]
Auntie, we need to go.
Pack up your things and Jasmin's.
We're going to leave this place.
But, Raul…
We're going to move somewhere else.
Just take your important stuff.
Raul…
Auntie, I've already made up my mind.
[whimpers]
This is perfect.
You're in a good mood.
Of course, Auntie.
And that's because Ivy has
already vowed to support me
on my campaign to build up
the party's confidence in me.
So this is it. [chuckles]
I'm going to be a senator now.
-Cheers.
But what if Julio comes back?
He can take everything away
from you, Emilia.
You should do everything that you have to.
Or else you will find yourself
back to your former life…
a slave to Julio.
Is that what you want?
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
What have you been screwing up
this time, Emilia?
[suspenseful sting]
Papa?
Yes, in the flesh.
Very much alive and kicking.
[suspenseful music playing]
He was one of Emilia's victims.
He worked in the municipal office.
He questioned her about the budget.
Yes, it was me. I killed him myself.
I killed this young man, too.
This one, too.
Did anyone order you to put
a ring on one of the corpses?
I only killed the victims.
But I'm not the one who buried them.
I don't know anything about a ring.
If you didn't bury them, then who did?
Mr. Noel.
He gathered the bodies,
and he's the one who dumped
and buried them, too.
And where can we find this Mr. Noel?
[tense music playing]
I know I've made a lot of mistakes, Papa.
But I did everything I could
to protect our name.
[Julio] How?
By proclaiming yourself as
the queen of Poblacion Ardiente?
By throwing out and having
the farmers killed?
Or having Senator Pablo murdered?
Is that how a decent leader acts?
No.
Because that's what an executioner does.
You disrespected our family's name.
This family has no room…
for dumb and shallow people,
who make stupid decisions!
Who do you think you are? Huh?
Who told you to take over
everything I left behind?
Huh?! No one!
You have no right sitting
in my goddamn chair!
Murdering my staff…
and claiming my position!
You aren't even worthy enough
to lick my boot.
And when I return…
I will need a new set of canes.
Because I assure you…
that I will break every single one of them
while hitting that thick skull of yours
to see if your brain will still run…
Or until you die and end up
on the roadside.
[suspenseful music playing]
[whimpers]
-[screams]
-[glass breaks]
[breathing heavily]
[suspenseful music playing]
[ominous music playing]
Jepoy, you can go.
[instrumental theme music playing]
Dad…
It's been a while.
[inhales]
Dad, I think Mom is still alive.
I can feel it, Dad.
And I hope I'm right.
I really hope Mom is alive.
Because I miss her so much.
You too, Dad.
I miss our family.
[inhales sharply]
So, I really hope my hunch is right.
I hope that Mom is still alive.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
I want to be with Mom again.
I really miss you both.
I miss you both so much.
I love you, Dad.
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
I'll find Mom.
I promise.
[Jepoy] Walk faster.
Go on.
Ivy.
[tense music playing]
I'm sorry, Camia.
I don't want to hurt you,
but I have to do this.
If I don't, I might lose you.
And I can't let that happen.
Because someday, we'll build a family.
We'll be happy together.
I promise you that, Camia.
[ominous music playing]
[Ivy] Noel.
You're Noel, right?
If you're the one who buries…
all of the Ardientes' victims…
then, are you…
are you the one who buried
my mother's body?
Who told you to do it?
With all the bodies I buried…
how could I remember them?
Besides…
I've been living peacefully
as a gravedigger.
As they say, it's more peaceful
to deal with the dead…
than the living.
Now if that's all, I'll go now.
It was 13 years ago
when they took my mother away.
[suspenseful sting]
Someone claimed she was dead…
replaced her with another body…
and put her ring on it.
[tense music playing]
A ring?
Did you say a ring?
This one.
[tense music playing]
I remember it now.
A man asked me to bury
a sack of human bones.
Then he told me…
to put this exact ring
on one of the fingers.
I remember it now.
Who told you to do it?
It was Raul.
Raul Torillo.
[suspenseful sting]
Raul Torillo?
The Raul Torillo?
He was the man who gave me
the sack of bones.
Why? Why would he ask you to do that?
I don't know.
[Jepoy] Listen to me.
Tell us the truth.
I really don't know. Believe me.
I was just following
the Ardientes' orders!
[Jepoy] Here.
I'm begging you…
Don't tell anyone about this conversation.
I worked for them for nine years.
I just did what they told me.
I didn't know who they were
or why I have to bury them.
[sobbing] But my conscience
is eating me up!
Maybe this is how
I can lighten the burden.
I pray…
that I was of help to you.
[tense music playing]
Raul.
It was Raul.
[breathing heavily]
Sit down.
[Raul clears throat]
Uh, love, I'm just packing up our things.
I'm packing because…
We're going to move somewhere else.
Somewhere new, bigger, and nicer.
[tense music playing]
Don't worry.
I'll always be here for you.
I'll take care of you.
Then we're going away from here.
We're going to live happily.
[tense music playing]
I just need to fix this.
[breathing heavily]
You're a monster, Raul! You--
You wretched bastard!
Dad, it was Raul!
Raul was the one who took Mom.
It was Raul.
Jepoy, everything started with Raul.
The reason--
He's the reason
why my family was targeted.
Why my mom was mad at the Ardientes.
This is Raul's fault.
And now, Raul has my mom.
Raul has my mom!
[breathing heavily]
Raul, you bastard…
You bastard.
Get ready, Raul…
because I'm going to take my mom back.
I'm going to take her back, Raul.
[inhales sharply]
It's Raul…
[screaming]
My mom is with Raul.
Dad, Raul has Mom…
Raul took Mom.
He's the one who took her.
[whimpering]
[Arnaldo] Okay, good.
Make sure that's complete.
Mayor…
The guests are arriving at the venue.
They're all excited for your birthday.
All right, good.
We're going to follow there.
Please entertain them in the meantime.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay?
All right. Double time, everyone.
Wow, burgers.
This is nice, Arnaldo.
Burgers… for the Mayor's birthday.
What a brilliant idea,
don't you think, Ivy?
Happy birthday. But where's your father?
-That's right.
-It's your birthday.
Is he coming, Mr. Mayor?
[Emilia] You know, Ivy has a point.
Your Daddy should be here
because, you know,
it's the birthday of
Señor Julio's favorite grandson.
You know, people might think
we have trouble in paradise
if he's not here, right, Ivy?
Where is he anyway?
[sighs]
Arnaldo!
Son, happy birthday.
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I'm a bit busy
with our business,
so I won't be able
to attend your birthday party.
[Arnaldo] You have to be there.
People will be looking for you.
I can't promise that, son.
I really have to focus on the business.
That's why I came here
to tell you in advance.
My goodness, Mr. Torillo.
Are you saying you have more
important stuff to attend to
than your son's birthday?
[Emilia sighs] Ivy is right again.
Is that errand of yours
more important than
your son's birthday, huh?
Right. And lately, we've been noticing
you're always out of the house.
What have you been up to lately?
Like what I said,
our business has me swamped.
I have to focus on it, son.
But if we're going to have
problems because of that…
if I really have to attend your
birthday, then I'll be there.
Wow! How perfect.
Now we are one big happy family, right?
Hmm…
-Happy birthday.
-Thank you.
-[Arnaldo] How are you?
-[man 1] Happy birthday, Mayor.
Thank you.
-[woman] This is from the Mayor.
-How are you? How's the burger?
[Arnaldo] You can always get more, okay?
Just tell them I sent you.
-[man 2] Thank you, Mayor.
-[Arnaldo] You're welcome.
-[man 3] Mayor, happy birthday.
-[woman 2] Happy birthday.
[Arnaldo] Thank you. Okay.
Go on, eat your fill.
-Happy birthday, Mayor.
-Thank you, ma'am. Thank you.
Just get your burgers there.
They're for everyone.
-[woman 3] Thank you, Mayor.
-[Arnaldo] Okay, take a seat.
Happy birthday, Mayor.
-Thank you, thank you.
-[man 4] Happy birthday, Mayor.
-[Arnaldo] Thank you very much.
-Ivy, I'll just be there.
I have to talk to my constituents.
Okay, Emilia.
[Arnaldo] How are you? Are you okay now?
[Emilia] Give some more
to the people at the back.
[tense music playing]
[Diego] Ivy.
Diego.
Wait, I have to talk to you.
-Um, can we just talk later?
-Ivy.
This won't take long, Ivy.
Uh, Diego…
Ivy, I didn't know you had a sister.
[tense music playing]
Why didn't you tell me?
Why are you keeping secrets?
[scoffs]
Uh…
[Ivy chuckles nervously]
Yes, Diego.
I had a sister.
I didn't tell you about her
because it's still a very
sensitive topic for me.
I guess you won't understand
because you've never lost
a loved one before.
Ivy…
I know the feeling.
I've lost someone, too.
Diego, Lily just disappeared.
She didn't die. They're different things.
You never told me about that.
How did…
How did Lily and her family disappear?
They went away without saying goodbye.
That's how they left?
Isn't that suspicious, Diego?
They didn't even say goodbye.
All I remember is her parents
had a fight with my dad.
I guess they left because
they didn't want any trouble.
[sighs]
They didn't want any trouble? Why?
Did your dad hurt Lily and her family?
Do you think your father
could do that, Diego?
Can he hurt other people?
Is he that kind of person?
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[inhales] Diego…
I don't know why you're suddenly
interested in my sister.
Are you doing a background check on me?
Are you still doubting me?
[exasperated sigh]
It's sad, but I think the saying is true…
that you can't please everyone.
Ivy, I'm sorry.
It's not my problem anymore, Diego,
if you don't trust me.
Excuse me.
Ivy…
[tense music playing]
[Arnaldo] Thank you very much
for celebrating my birthday with me.
This day wouldn't be special
if it weren't for you.
Thank you very much.
[crowd applauding]
[woman] Happy birthday, Mayor.
[Arnaldo] And since everyone
is here already,
and you're all part
of the Ardiente-Torillo family,
I'm sure everyone will be happy
to hear the news.
My birthday wish was just
fulfilled earlier this day.
I spoke to my grandfather's
doctor in America,
and he told me the good news,
that Señor Julio is out of his coma.
And the doctor also told me
that my grandfather
is on the road to recovery.
Just a few more days…
our beloved Congressman,
Señor Julio Ardiente, will return!
[crowd applauding, cheering]
Viva Ardiente!
-[crowd] Viva Ardiente!
-One more! Viva Ardiente!
[crowd] Viva Ardiente!
[tense music playing]
Once Julio sets foot
in Poblacion Ardiente,
it'll be the end for you, Emilia.
You have to do something.
Auntie, I'm the one who's going
to be dead, not you.
I have a solution to all my problems here.
I'll treat him like one of my enemies.
You're going to have Julio killed?
[tense music playing]
He's your father.
Then I'll write him a nice eulogy.
I'll erect a big statue in his honor.
I'll even cry for him.
But Poblacion Ardiente
is too small for the both of us.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hello?
I have a new assignment for you.
Before this day ends, I want him dead.
[suspenseful music playing]
No, no, no, no!
I shouldn't have confronted her.
I shouldn't have asked about her sister.
It's only normal for you to ask.
You're friends.
You're close, right?
And it's like she's keeping
something from me, Nanny.
What do you think it is?
I don't know, but I want to know her more.
-[Loring] I understand.
-Because I love her, Nanny.
What?!
Hey, hey, hey! That's something else!
That's something else! [chuckles]
-Hold on.
-Hey! Hey, wait.
Hey!
Why, Diego?
[giggles] Why?
Why don't you tell her?
Just confess it.
Hey.
[sighs]
[both chuckle]
I knew it.
You know, you might be very handsome now.
You might be taller and all.
Your muscles might be bulging.
But until now,
you are still the chubby Diego,
my shy little boy!
Diego, you have nothing to be ashamed of
if your feelings are true!
[Loring and Pandoy giggling]
[Pandoy] Come on.
[Loring] Tell her now how you feel.
Confess your feelings so
she won't be mad at you anymore.
Okay?
So she'll understand. Who knows?
She might tell you, "I love you, too."
[giggles]
[sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[Julio] Who told you
to take over everything I left behind?
You have no right sitting
in my goddamn chair!
You aren't even worthy enough
to lick my boot.
[Claire] It'll be the end for you, Emilia.
You have to do something.
[Emilia] Before this day ends,
I want him dead.
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[sniffles, sobs]
[laughing]
[inhales, exhales sharply]
[suspenseful music playing]
Tonight, your problems
will finally disappear, Emilia.
I will miss you, Papa.
[laughing maniacally]
[suspenseful music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
-[man 1] Cheers!
-[Arnaldo] Cheers! All right!
Nice.
Great. I'm going to get some later.
How are my party-mates here?
[man 2] Happy birthday, Mayor.
[Arnaldo] We might not have our guns here,
but we can always go hunting.
Arnaldo!
Hey, Mom.
-Happy birthday, son.
-Thank you. Thank you.
[Raul] Happy birthday, Arnaldo.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy your party, okay?
I will.
[Emilia] I'll just talk to some friends.
-[Arnaldo] Okay.
-[Raul] See you in a while.
-Happy birthday.
-[Arnaldo] Thank you.
-Happy birthday, Mayor.
-Thank you.
[Arnaldo] Take care of our guests.
Just keep the alcohol flowing.
Hi, Mr. Mayor. Happy, happy birthday.
Thank you.
As promised… Surprise!
[Arnaldo chuckles]
I hope you like it.
-This is beautiful.
-[chuckles]
Thank you very much.
I've been planning to buy
this gun ever since.
And now I have it.
[chuckles]
Do you like it?
It's perfect.
[upbeat music playing]
Can I just say that you look
so beautiful tonight.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
[upbeat music playing]
Take this inside.
Happy birthday.
I don't remember inviting you,
but now you're here.
Thank you.
Feel at home.
Enjoy the party.
We have a lot of women here.
I can introduce you.
Excuse me.
[upbeat music playing]
[line ringing]
[Raul] Hello?
All right. Just update me.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Okay, I'll go there later.
Okay. Thank you.
Hi.
Hi, Mr. Torillo.
-You look stressed.
-[Raul chuckles]
Is something wrong?
Here, this one's for you.
Thanks.
Well, since you asked about my problems…
Yes, I have a lot.
But it's none of your business.
Mr. Torillo…
It's your son's birthday.
Yeah, I know.
Let's have fun?
[chuckles]
You don't have to ask, Mr. Torillo…
but I know a lot of ways
to relieve stress.
You can wait for me here.
-And then…
-[chuckles]
I'll come back for you.
Cheers?
Wait for me.
[tense music playing]
Hey, wait a second.
I just need to use the toilet.
[phone ringing]
[line ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
Hello?
Hello? Are you with Camia Cruz?
[suspenseful sting]
Hello?
[suspenseful music playing]
Happy birthday, my favorite grandson!
-How are you there in the States?
-[Julio] I'm good.
And when I return,
I will clean up the trash that
gathered there while I was away.
[Emilia] He will regret coming back
here to Poblacion Ardiente.
I will make his life a living hell.
Mayor, some of our men saw Miss Aguas
following Mr. Raul outside
of Poblacion Ardiente.
[screaming]
-Raul, Jasmin got away!
-Where is Jasmin?!
[Belen] Look for her!
Mom?
[tense music playing]